<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Wonky Beans</title>
    <link>https://beans.nfshost.com/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Wonky Beans</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <managingEditor>blue.lazer.dad@gmail.com (Aiden Hsu)</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>blue.lazer.dad@gmail.com (Aiden Hsu)</webMaster>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 18 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://beans.nfshost.com/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Star Wars Battlefront II</title>
      <link>https://beans.nfshost.com/2021/01/star-wars-battlefront2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>blue.lazer.dad@gmail.com (Aiden Hsu)</author>
      <guid>https://beans.nfshost.com/2021/01/star-wars-battlefront2/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I play this game called Star Wars Battlefront II. What is that you ask?
Well let me explain.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Battlefront II (can be abbreviated to BF2, but not to be confused with Battlefield 2, which is a different game) is a game featuring a wide variety of modes, and there are two ways to play. First, you can play the story mode, which takes you on a journey through the perspective of individuals amongst the universe at that point of time. The online play is, well, online. You can join and queue into different varieties that online mode has to offer with your friends or strangers. 
They are all different and similar in different aspects, and it also give you the option to choose timelines, meaning you can play modes like Supremacy during the Age of the Republic, Age of the Empire, or Age of the Resistance.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Whatever game you join, it is teeming with potential to help you become better at the game while enabling you to have fun, as the mechanics and different abilities that come with whatever you play always adds some thrill to the battle.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This was a little short, but I think it gets the idea across. I fully recommend this game to everyone and until January 21st, it will be free for people to download and play on the Epic Games store.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;And as always, may the force be with you.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Star Wars Jedi: Fallen Order</title>
      <link>https://beans.nfshost.com/2021/01/star-wars-jedi/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>blue.lazer.dad@gmail.com (Aiden Hsu)</author>
      <guid>https://beans.nfshost.com/2021/01/star-wars-jedi/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Star Wars Jedi: Fallen Order is a single-player story game that takes you through the life of a Jedi named Cal Kestis, who was a padawan to Jedi Master Jaro Tapal, who was killed during the Jedi Purge, which led to Cal going into hiding and living alone, becoming a scrapper on Bracca, the planet which they were stationed on when Order 66 was issued.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Fallen Order has a very rich story, taking you back to when Cal was still training as a padawan through flashbacks during his journey to rebuild the Jedi Order. I can&amp;rsquo;t say much about the game, as I have only seen videos on what is going to happen later on even though I&amp;rsquo;m still very new to all this. I had only started playing this recently, but I have enjoyed every moment of it thus far. I have been on 4 planets only, those being Bracca, Bogano, Zeffos, and Kashyyk. Right now, I am on Kashyyk helping the infamous rebel Saw Gerrera as he continues to resist the Empire. Before that, I&amp;rsquo;ve found a tomb of a sage on Zeffos, explored an ancient Jedi vault, and learned the basic controls on Bracca, where the game started.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The game has this more or less unique feature called meditation circles, which are practically checkpoints. It also has 2 other options, such as Rest, which replenishes his health bar, and things like that. But the con is that all enemies respawn, so if there was a particularly tough enemy, such as a Purge Trooper, you will need to fight them again. It also has a skill tree, where you can spend skill points earned by fighting enemies and discovering things. The skill points can be spent on abilities like more health, advanced lightsaber combat techniques, and force abilities. There are just 3 categories I know of in the skill tree, and they are Force, Lightsaber, and Survival.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So yeah, this has been me talking about Star Wars Jedi: Fallen Order&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I read Wings of Fire</title>
      <link>https://beans.nfshost.com/2021/01/wings-of-fire/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>blue.lazer.dad@gmail.com (Aiden Hsu)</author>
      <guid>https://beans.nfshost.com/2021/01/wings-of-fire/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The &amp;ldquo;Wings of Fire&amp;rdquo; are a series of New York Times bestseller books written by Tui T. Sutherland. It is fictional writing about dragons and fantasy, but with a bit more violence. Some of the details are quite gruesome, if I do say so myself. But nevertheless, I am on the last book of the series, so I decided to write a short summary of the first book and the others in order (separate essays of course).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The book is centred around 5 characters, who are dragons. Their names are Clay, Tsunami, Sunny, Glory, and Starflight. These 5 dragons are called the &amp;ldquo;Dragonets of Destiny&amp;rdquo; and it was written in a prophecy that they would end the great dragon war, which has been going on for 18 years now. Those 5 dragonets are different types of dragons, Clay is a MudWing, Tsunami is a SeaWing, Sunny is a SandWing, Glory is a RainWing, and Starflight is a NightWing. All of the dragon species names are IceWing, SkyWing, NightWing, RainWing, SeaWing, MudWing, and SandWing.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;These 5 dragons start off under a mountain, being taken away as eggs and left to three dragons named Dune, Webs, and Kestrel. They are part of an organization called the &amp;ldquo;Talons of Peace&amp;rdquo;, who are dedicated to making sure the prophecy is fulfilled so the war can come to an end. The dragonets don&amp;rsquo;t like living underground, as it&amp;rsquo;s not very natural and their guardians are harsh to them. Eventually, they escape, but at the cost of being captured by SkyWing queen Queen Scarlet. Clay, Tsunami, Glory, Sunny, and Starflight are taken as prisoners to the Sky Kingdom, where Clay, Tsunami and Starflight are held in the prisons to be made to fight in the arena for Queen Scarlet&amp;rsquo;s entertainment. The dragonets manage to get out of that pickle with some inside help. The dragonets go on a quest to try to find Clay&amp;rsquo;s family, where he learns some disappointing news. The story then ends when the dragonets decide that they will try to find Tsunami&amp;rsquo;s family.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Each book is written from a different dragonets point of view, meaning most of the book is focused from the eye of an individual dragon. The first book, titled &amp;ldquo;The Dragonet Prophecy&amp;rdquo; is written from Clay&amp;rsquo;s experiences.
The second book is written from Tsunami&amp;rsquo;s, the third book is written from Glory&amp;rsquo;s, the fourth book is written from Starflight&amp;rsquo;s, and the fifth book is written from Sunny&amp;rsquo;s.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A short story</title>
      <link>https://beans.nfshost.com/2021/01/short-story/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>blue.lazer.dad@gmail.com (Aiden Hsu)</author>
      <guid>https://beans.nfshost.com/2021/01/short-story/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Our story starts in a modern day town house, focused on a kid named Aiden. This particular child loved video games, and aspired to be a professional gamer. And a part of that dream was acquiring the best gaming gear he can get. But, since he was only a teenager still depending on his parents, Aiden had to start small. He had it good, no doubt, with an amazing keyboard and mouse, a decent pc, and a decent headset. But the next thing he wanted was a better microphone, so he started asking his dad for one. But his dad was reluctant at first, making excuses to brush off his son by complaining about the price, or how it make no difference, saying that it would be useless and just take up space. He would even completely ignore or bounce around the question at times. But then came December, and Aiden was making moves. He had recently acquired Steam, the game streaming platform, and had gotten a ton of money for Christmas, so he decided to treat himself on games. He was still trying to find a way to get that mic, but soon, an epiphany dawned on him. The only way Aiden was going to get that mic was if it went on sale. Aiden was still waiting and waiting for the mic to go on sale. But seeing as it had not during the time he was checking vigilantly, his hope started to dwindle, and at points where he even gave up all hope. Then one morning, Aiden woke up to a sunny sky and checked the price. It had dropped! The miracle brought sheer joy to Aiden on that sunny morning, lifting his spirits as high as it could go that day. Soon, his dad learnt of the sale and ordered the mic for Aiden. The rest is, as they say, history.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Writing to waste time</title>
      <link>https://beans.nfshost.com/2020/12/writing/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>blue.lazer.dad@gmail.com (Aiden Hsu)</author>
      <guid>https://beans.nfshost.com/2020/12/writing/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Hello there. My name is beans and I&amp;rsquo;m going to sit here and write this essay because I need to write an essay and also to waste time. So um, while I&amp;rsquo;m here, I might as well talk about today. I had a pretty good day actually, and it is still pretty good because at the time of writing the day is still not over. My dad is gonna buy me a new mic because it&amp;rsquo;s one that I&amp;rsquo;ve sought after for quite a bit of time now, it&amp;rsquo;s cheap, and it&amp;rsquo;s a good quality microphone. I might get back into making YouTube videos again, with the new equipment, and let&amp;rsquo;s see how it goes. What&amp;rsquo;s funny about my YouTube channel is that through almost no effort at all in the past 8-9 months that I have gotten to 50 subscribers, which is honestly amazing. Another new thing I&amp;rsquo;ve gotten into doing is just saying the word honk randomly. For example, one of my friends will just have discord open on the side while they&amp;rsquo;re playing a game or just chilling, and then they&amp;rsquo;ll randomly see a messages in a mutual server or messages that we have, and it&amp;rsquo;ll just be me saying the word honk. It doesn&amp;rsquo;t always have to be just normal honk, I can also vary it sometimes if it fancies me. Anyhow, my goal for this essay was at least 230 words, and seeing as I have surpassed that goal, I will now end it here.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Bye, and until next time.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My keyboard and mouse</title>
      <link>https://beans.nfshost.com/2020/12/keyboard-mouse/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>blue.lazer.dad@gmail.com (Aiden Hsu)</author>
      <guid>https://beans.nfshost.com/2020/12/keyboard-mouse/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Today I will write a short little piece about my keyboard and mouse, and what impact they&amp;rsquo;ve had on me.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;My keyboard and mouse are recent additions to my gaming setup, along with my headset, computer and mousepad. Before I got my keyboard and mouse, I was using my dad&amp;rsquo;s crappy office peripherals to play Minecraft. It wasn&amp;rsquo;t the best, but it worked. As time went on, I watched YouTube videos about gaming peripherals, such as the keyboard and mouse I have now. The ones I ended up buying is the Corsair K68 Mechanical Keyboard, with Cherry MX Red switches. My mouse is the Razer DeathAdder Elite. These peripherals have helped me win numerous amounts of games, no matter what I play. The senior of these is the DeathAdder, which I got last year as a birthday present. The keyboard was 
acquired in August of the same year, when I had grew to think my dad&amp;rsquo;s Rosewill mechanical keyboard with blue switches intolerable. I prefer a quieter and less tactile keyboard as compared to a more tactile and clickier keyboard, while my dad preferred the latter.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I really adore my keyboard and mouse, and every time I go to play video games I get excited because of the knowledge that my keyboard and mouse will enable me to have fun with my friends, or just alone. Whenever I am playing well with my keyboard and mouse, they don&amp;rsquo;t feel like objects anymore. They feel like an extension of my body that will do what I will it to. And I think that&amp;rsquo;s great, because that&amp;rsquo;s what they&amp;rsquo;re made to do.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Music Assignment</title>
      <link>https://beans.nfshost.com/2020/12/music-assignment/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>blue.lazer.dad@gmail.com (Aiden Hsu)</author>
      <guid>https://beans.nfshost.com/2020/12/music-assignment/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The composers that I chose to compare are John Williams and Ludwig van Beethoven. The songs that I chose were &amp;ldquo;The Imperial March&amp;rdquo;, composed by John Williams, and Ode To Joy, which was composed by Ludwig van Beethoven.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Let me start off by talking about John Williams. John Towner Williams was born on February 8, 1932 in Flushing, New York. He is an American composer, conductor, pianist and trombonist. He is also considered the greatest film composer of all time by a great many people. John Williams has composed some of the most famous film scores for movies, such as the Star Wars saga, Jaws, Close Encounters of the Third Kind, Superman, E.T. the Extra-Terrestrial, Home Alone, the Indiana Jones movies, the first two Jurassic Park movies, Schindler&amp;rsquo;s List, and the first three Harry Potter movies. Williams has also composed a number of classical concertos and other pieces of music for orchestral ensembles and solo instruments. He has also worked with movie director Steven Spielberg since 1974, composing music for all but five of his movies. Other works by Williams include theme music for the 1984 Summer Olympic Games, NBC Sunday Night Football, &amp;ldquo;The Mission&amp;rdquo; theme used by NBC News and Seven News in Australia, the television series Lost in Space and Land of the Giants, and the incidental music for the first season of Gilligan&amp;rsquo;s Island. He has composed the score for eight of the top 25 highest-grossing movies at the U.S. box office. His work has influenced other movie composers and contemporary classical and popular music. John Williams has won 25 Grammy Awards, seven British Academy Film Awards, five Academy Awards, and four Golden Globe Awards.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Imperial March does not have any lyrics, but here is the link to listen to it. It is 3:50 seconds long. 
Link: https:https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=vsMWVW4xtwI&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Ludwig van Beethoven was born in December 1770, in Bonn, Germany. He was a German composer and pianist. Beethoven remains one of the most admired composers in the history of Western music, as his works ranks amongst the most performed classical music pieces. His works span the transition from the classical period to the romantic era in classical music. His career has been divided into early, middle, and late periods. The &amp;ldquo;early&amp;rdquo; period of his career, in which he was developing his skill, is typically considered to have lasted until 1802. From 1802 to 1812, the &amp;ldquo;middle&amp;rdquo; period of his career showed a unique path from the &amp;ldquo;classical&amp;rdquo; styles of Joseph Haydn and Wolfgang Amadeus Mozart, and this choice is sometimes characterized as &amp;ldquo;heroic&amp;rdquo;. It was during this time when Beethoven began to suffer from deafness. During the &amp;ldquo;late&amp;rdquo; period of his career, which was from 1812 to the time of his death, he lengthened his innovations in musical form and expression.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Ode To Joy was originally written in German, so here are the German lyrics and then the English translation. This is the link to listen to it: &lt;a href=&#34;https://youtu.be/ChygZLpJDNE&#34;&gt;https://youtu.be/ChygZLpJDNE&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Lyrics: (German)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;An die Freude&amp;rdquo;
Freude, schöner Götterfunken,
Tochter aus Elysium,
Wir betreten feuertrunken,
Himmlische, dein Heiligtum!
Deine Zauber binden wieder
Was die Mode streng geteilt;
Alle Menschen werden Brüder
Wo dein sanfter Flügel weilt.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Wem der große Wurf gelungen
Eines Freundes Freund zu sein;
Wer ein holdes Weib errungen
Mische seinen Jubel ein!
Ja, wer auch nur eine Seele
Sein nennt auf dem Erdenrund!
Und wer&amp;rsquo;s nie gekonnt, der stehle
Weinend sich aus diesem Bund!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Freude trinken alle Wesen
An den Brüsten der Natur;
Alle Guten, alle Bösen
Folgen ihrer Rosenspur.
Küsse gab sie uns und Reben,
Einen Freund, geprüft im Tod;
Wollust ward dem Wurm gegeben
und der Cherub steht vor Gott.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Froh, wie seine Sonnen fliegen
Durch des Himmels prächt&amp;rsquo;gen Plan
Laufet, Brüder, eure Bahn,
Freudig, wie ein Held zum siegen.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Seid umschlungen, Millionen!
Diesen Kuß der ganzen Welt!
Brüder, über&amp;rsquo;m Sternenzelt
Muß ein lieber Vater wohnen.
Ihr stürzt nieder, Millionen?
Ahnest du den Schöpfer, Welt?
Such&#39; ihn über&amp;rsquo;m Sternenzelt!
Über Sternen muß er wohnen.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This is the English translation:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;Ode To Joy&amp;rdquo;
Joy, beautiful spark of Divinity [or: of gods],
Daughter of Elysium,
We enter, drunk with fire,
Heavenly one, thy sanctuary!
Thy magic binds again
What custom strictly divided;*
All people become brothers,*
Where thy gentle wing abides.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Whoever has succeeded in the great attempt,
To be a friend&amp;rsquo;s friend,
Whoever has won a lovely woman,
Add his to the jubilation!
Yes, and also whoever has just one soul
To call his own in this world!
And he who never managed it should slink 
Weeping from this union!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;All creatures drink of joy
At nature&amp;rsquo;s breasts.
All the Just, all the Evil
Follow her trail of roses.
Kisses she gave us and grapevines,
A friend, proven in death.
Salaciousness was given to the worm 
And the cherub stands before God.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Gladly, as His suns fly
through the heavens&#39; grand plan 
Go on, brothers, your way,
Joyful, like a hero to victory.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Be embraced, Millions!
This kiss to all the world!
Brothers, above the starry canopy
There must dwell a loving Father.
Are you collapsing, millions?
Do you sense the creator, world?
Seek him above the starry canopy!
Above stars must He dwell.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Now I will compare the two songs. Firstly, Ode To Joy was written and still remains to this day as a protest anthem and a celebration of music. Ode To Joy is part of the classical music genre, while Imperial March is part of the film soundtrack genre. Imperial March is one of the best known symphonic movie themes, and it is an example of a leitmotif, which is a recurrent theme associated with characters or events in drama. Ode To Joy is seen as the greatest of Beethoven&amp;rsquo;s work by numerous critics and musicologists. It is also considered one of the supreme achievements in the history of music.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A short synopsis of Hamilton: An American Musical</title>
      <link>https://beans.nfshost.com/2020/12/hamilton/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>blue.lazer.dad@gmail.com (Aiden Hsu)</author>
      <guid>https://beans.nfshost.com/2020/12/hamilton/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Hamilton is a sung-and-rapped through musical which portrayed the life of Founding Father Alexander Hamilton. The show draws heavily from hip hop, as well as R&amp;amp;B, pop, soul, and traditional show tunes. The show also had non-white actors cast as the Founding Fathers and other historical figures. Lin Manuel Miranda described the musical as &amp;ldquo;America then, as told by America now.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Since the opening on Broadway, Hamilton received critical acclaim. It premiered Off-Broadway, at the Public Theater, on February 17, 2015. The musical won eight Drama Desk awards, including Outstanding Musical. Then it was performed at the Richards Rodgers Theater on Broadway, opening on August 6, 2015, where it received positive reviews and high box office sales. At the 2016 Tony Awards, Hamilton received a record-breaking 16 nominations and won 11 awards, including Best Musical. It also received the Pulitzer Prize for 2016.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A production of Hamilton in Chicago began previewing performances at the CIBC Theater in September 2016 and opened the following month. The West End production opened at the Victoria Palace Theatre in London in December 2017, winning seven Olivier Awards in 2018, including Best New Musical. The first U.S. national tour began in March 2017, and a second U.S. tour opened in February 2018, and Hamilton&amp;rsquo;s third U.S. tour began January 11, 2019, with a three-week engagement in Puerto Rico featuring Miranda as the titular character, Hamilton.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sandwich</title>
      <link>https://beans.nfshost.com/2020/11/sandwich/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>blue.lazer.dad@gmail.com (Aiden Hsu)</author>
      <guid>https://beans.nfshost.com/2020/11/sandwich/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Ah, the majestic sandwich. It is a simple invention, but exquisite. The more known use for it is to consume and sate hunger, but there are other uses as well, such as a projectile in a food fight.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The sandwich originates from 18th-century Europe John Montagu, 4th Earl of Sandwich. He was supposedly the inventor of the sandwich. However, the modern-day sandwich is named after Lord Sandwich, who was a constant gambler and didn&amp;rsquo;t have time to eat proper meals, so he kept asking his servants to bring him slices of meat between two slices of bread. His gambling friends were well versed with this habit, so some of them started saying, &amp;ldquo;I&amp;rsquo;ll have the same as Sandwich!&amp;rdquo;, and thus the &amp;ldquo;sandwich&amp;rdquo; was born.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Sandwiches are very easy to make, requiring little to no skill. I personally have done so numerous times.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Well, there&amp;rsquo;s my little informative on sandwiches.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Winter and cold things in general</title>
      <link>https://beans.nfshost.com/2020/11/winter/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>blue.lazer.dad@gmail.com (Aiden Hsu)</author>
      <guid>https://beans.nfshost.com/2020/11/winter/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;When a conversation with some people or a subject in class comes to seasons, and I get asked which season I prefer the most, my answer is always winter. I mean, you see the word &amp;ldquo;winter&amp;rdquo; everywhere. For instance, Wintergreen, Winter solstice, Winter season, and that&amp;rsquo;s about all the &amp;ldquo;winter-y&amp;rdquo; things I can think to list. I mean, what&amp;rsquo;s not to like about the cold season? Not the &amp;ldquo;cold&amp;rdquo; season as in the ailment, but cold as in temperature. In winter, there&amp;rsquo;s hockey, Christmas, Advent, a few hours long mass at night until midnight, Christmas Eve excitement which is a bit dampened by the Christmas mass, cookies, baking, decoration, parties (none this year, which $!#%^*! sucks), and all the presents.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Ok, granted, I didn&amp;rsquo;t mention all the kindness, giving, you get the gist. That goes without saying, right? I mean, year-round people are preaching to be nice to everyone. You&amp;rsquo;ve got teachers in school, the priest, beggars, random strangers that like to point it out sometimes.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I know that the police also have kindness as a part of their mission statement. However, as of now, that&amp;rsquo;s hypocritical of some cops considering that there&amp;rsquo;s a lot of police brutality stories circulating on social media, but then again, not all cops are mean.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Right now in Canada, the last week of November is when it usually starts to get colder and starts snowing a bit. And as of typing this, I am in the last week of November, and it had just snowed heavily a few hours ago. And I don&amp;rsquo;t mean powder snow, I mean packing snow. The snow that&amp;rsquo;s normally turned into snowballs.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Anyway, I&amp;rsquo;ve got a theory. In 1939, when the Soviet Union invaded Finland, which was named the Winter War, the Finnish soldiers somehow staved off the attack (even though the Russians had superior military strength, especially in tanks and aircraft), and pushed them back into Moscow. Long story short, Maybe the Finnish soldiers used snowballs against the Russians. What if they hid grenades in them?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Well, thanks for reading my essay about winter and cold things in general.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Petition Against Essays</title>
      <link>https://beans.nfshost.com/2020/11/no-essays/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>blue.lazer.dad@gmail.com (Aiden Hsu)</author>
      <guid>https://beans.nfshost.com/2020/11/no-essays/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;A petition against essays (for me)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So, I have a problem of sorts. Every week, my Dad is compelling me to write an essay about something. It was fine the first time because it was a new thing to do. The second time was also ok, but the excitement was wearing off indefinitely. I did write about breakfast, which was fun, but it took me all week because I didn&amp;rsquo;t enjoy it that much. And now, I&amp;rsquo;m doing the third essay, which is this one, and I&amp;rsquo;m not enjoying writing this. Today is Tuesday, and this essay was supposed to be due Sunday, meaning a few days ago, so here we are. That&amp;rsquo;s my point! This task of writing every week is an emotional burden on me, consistently pressuring me into penmanship on a computer, and one day, I&amp;rsquo;m going to snap, with my head exploding like an overripe squash getting heated in an industrial-sized oven.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So, I petition to stop this madness! All I need is your signature on the petition. To help me stop the constant barrage of words haunting my sight every day. We need to emancipate from the brutality and the tyranny of essays. Who cares if I have to write one? Why? Why should I be subjected to the horror of splattering words on a sheet of non-existent paper to satisfy the need of a starving consumer&amp;rsquo;s eyes. I ask myself, &amp;ldquo;Why do I need to sweat about my grammar and endlessly pore over sentences on a screen?&amp;rdquo; So say it with me. End irrelevant and useless essays. End the need for 500-word pieces of work. End the paragraphs of repetitive content, written with the intent of filling space and escaping the drudgery of having to write. Help me win this war against the overbearing dictators we have come to know as &amp;ldquo;Essays&amp;rdquo; Thank you for listening to my Ted Talk.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Breakfast</title>
      <link>https://beans.nfshost.com/2020/11/breakfast/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>blue.lazer.dad@gmail.com (Aiden Hsu)</author>
      <guid>https://beans.nfshost.com/2020/11/breakfast/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I think breakfast is a great thing. It&amp;rsquo;s a great way to start your day for one, and two, it&amp;rsquo;s a bunch of food in the morning. And the breakfast items are great as well. And you can virtually have anything. For starters, the regular breakfast items are toast, cereal, fruits, yogurt, eggs, coffee, oatmeal, sausages, bacon, kippers, black pudding, tea, baked beans, hash browns, milk, waffles etc.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;And then there&amp;rsquo;s the &amp;ldquo;I don&amp;rsquo;t care, let me eat whatever I want.&amp;rdquo; type of people. A prime example of one of those types of people is me. Sometimes, I will eat cake, pizza, cookies, overall sugary and generally unhealthy &amp;ldquo;breakfast&amp;rdquo; items. If there was a party or some event that happened the night before resulting in me acquiring these specific foods, then I will usually indulge in them the next morning, without holding back.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I have the mentality of I live to eat, instead of what my mother says, which is &amp;ldquo;You eat to live!&amp;rdquo; whenever I&amp;rsquo;m gorging myself a lot. I think it can work both ways, depending on the context, but I like the former better. Because then, I can use that to excuse myself to get more food at buffets.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When I do use that excuse, I usually beeline towards the desert bar. I get very excited by dessert, or candy, or chocolate, or just sugar that I like. Even though I don&amp;rsquo;t put the other desserts in the same cohort as ice cream, I think they are still pretty great.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Back to breakfast. Breakfast can be something that you can be very passionate about because it is a great topic to discuss. Breakfast is the first meal of the day after your stomach has abstained from it for a whole sleep cycle unless you&amp;rsquo;re the type of person that wakes up in the middle of the night for some snack (not that I have a problem with that. I&amp;rsquo;ve gone and done that quite a few times myself actually). Hence the word, breakfast, which means you break your fast.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Breakfast can be a very energizing and refreshing event in the morning, but it all depends on how the day is going. I, personally, think that all breakfasts should be an exciting beginning to the day, but then again, that&amp;rsquo;s just my opinion. And then again, you can also have your thoughts and views.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Enjoy your future breakfasts!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Day 1 in Minecraft</title>
      <link>https://beans.nfshost.com/2020/10/minecraft-day1/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 31 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>blue.lazer.dad@gmail.com (Aiden Hsu)</author>
      <guid>https://beans.nfshost.com/2020/10/minecraft-day1/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I woke up in the middle of a forest. It was morning. The sun was high up. The sky was bright. Too bright. My eyes were struggling to cope with the harsh light as I got to my feet. I looked at my surroundings and found nothing out of the ordinary. All there was is a bunch of grass, dirt, trees, chickens, pigs, and cows. Wait, chickens, pigs, and cows? I usually don&amp;rsquo;t see these in the wild. I thought they were all kept on farms. And I am quite hungry. Hm. Never mind. I&amp;rsquo;ll think about food later. Right now, something is telling me I need to get some wood for tools. But how am I supposed to get the wood? I have no axe. Out of frustration, I punched a tree. At first, I thought it would hurt like hell, but it was surprisingly not. And when I looked up, expecting to see a bruised or bleeding fist, all I saw was a tiny crack in the wood where my fist made contact. And from then on, I went around to a bunch of trees, taking their logs and turning them into planks. After some time, I came across a village just as night was falling. And after a quick conversation with some of the villagers, they let me sleep in one of their homes. I&amp;rsquo;m going to bed now. Let&amp;rsquo;s see what&amp;rsquo;s going to happen tomorrow.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Signing off,
BlueLazerDad&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
